Guide to the A.I.R. Gallery Archives MSS.184
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Administrative records
  - Subseries C: Minutes
    - Minutes from member meetings, Nov. 1972-Sep. 1981 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Minutes from member meetings, Sept. 1982-July 1985 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Minutes from member meetings, Sept. 1985-July 1988 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Minutes from member meetings, Sept. 1988-July 1989 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Minutes from member meetings, Sept. 1989-July 1990 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Minutes from member meetings, Sept. 1990-July 1991 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Minutes from member meetings, Sept. 1991-July 1992 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Minutes from member meetings, Sept. 1992-July 1993 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Minutes from member meetings, Sept. 1993-July 1994 (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Minutes from member meetings, Sept. 1994-July 1995 (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Minutes from member meetings, Sept. 1995-July 1996 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Minutes from member meetings, Dec. 1996 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Minutes from Board of Directors meetings, 1979-1988 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Minutes from Executive Committee meetings, 1972-1980 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Minutes and budget from Partnership meetings, 1988-1981 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Misc. meeting notes, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Subseries D: Membership (Members/affiliates/job descriptions) (see also Oversize)
    - Members - committee reports, 1981-1992 (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - Members - contracts, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - Members - description of membership, 1976-1983 (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - Members - form letters, 1972-? (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - Members - inquiries for membership, 1973-1984 (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Members - inquiries for membership, 1988-1993 (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - Members - lists of members, 1972-1988 (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - Members - lists of members, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - Members - lists of members (Committees), 1972-1995 (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - Members - lists of members (Directors), 1981-1987 (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - Members - resignation letters, 1973-1985 (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - Members - resignation letters, 1988-2004 (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - Members - slide scripts, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - Members - surveys/questionnaires (misc.), n.d. (Box 2, Folder 96)
    - Members - surveys/questionnaires (misc.), 1981-1992 (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - Members - surveys/questionnaires (misc.), 1981-1992 (Box 2, Folder 98)
    - Members - surveys/questionnaires re: "Feminist Art and Practice", 1981-1992 (Box 2, Folder 99)
    - Members - surveys/questionnaires re: organization of A.I.R., 1981-1992 (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - Affiliates - lists of members, 1986-1984 (Box 2, Folder 101)
    - Affiliates - program description, 1983-1987 (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - Affiliates - resignation letters, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 103)
    - Affiliates - resumes, 1983-1988(?) (Box 2, Folder 104)
    - Affiliates - slides, 1980-1987 (Box 2, Folder 105)
    - Affiliates - surveys/questionnaires, 1996( (Box 2, Folder 106)
    - Job descriptions - coordinator, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - Job descriptions - director, 1980-1988 (Box 3, Folder 108)
    - Job descriptions - director, 1988-1998 (Box 3, Folder 109)
    - Job descriptions - internship program, 1973-1991 (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - Job descriptions - internship program - former interns, 1992-1997 (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - Job descriptions - internship program - recommendation letters, 1980-1994 (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - Subseries E: Programming (see also Oversize)
    - General files, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - Announcements, 1972-1976 (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - Announcements, 1977-1981 (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - Announcements, 1982-1986 (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - Announcements, 1987-1991 (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - Announcements, 1992-1996 (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - Announcements, 1997-2001 (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - Chronology of exhibitions, 1972-1995 (Box 3, Folder 120)
    - Current Issues/Monday Evening programs, 1973-1987 (Box 3, Folder 121)
    - Emerging Artists - development, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 122)
    - Emerging Artists - form letters, 1986-1989 (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - Emerging Artists - Program #1: Kim Abeles, n.d. (Box 99, Folder 124)
    - Emerging Artists - Program #2: Dalia Mieri, n.d. (Box 99, Folder 125)
    - Emerging Artists - Program #3: Delyn Williams/Gail Swithenbank, n.d. (Box 99, Folder 126)
    - Emerging Artists - Program #4: Susan Miller/Maggie Poor/Marcia Godosky, n.d. (Box 99, Folder 127)
    - Emerging Artists - Program #5: Kumi Korf/Leigh Burton/Fran Cox/Jan O'Dea, n.d. (Box 99, Folder 128)
    - Emerging Artists - Program #6: Barbara Zucker, curator/RG Solbert/Catherine Hall/Meg Walker/Kathleen Schneider/Aurore Chabot/Joan Curtis, n.d. (Box 99, Folder 129)
    - Emerging Artists - Program #7: Susan Putterman, curator/Jennifer Macdonald/S. Chavchavardse/Deborah Beblo/Grace Wapner/Michel Demanche, n.d. (Box 99, Folder 130)
    - Emerging Artists - Program #9: Janet Heit, curator/Stefan Blyn/Cheryl Peterka, n.d. (Box 99, Folder 131)
    - Emerging Artists - Program: Bonnie Lucas, curator/Joan Nelson/Jane Irish, n.d. (Box 99, Folder 132)
    - Emerging Artists - Slide scripts, n.d. (Box 99, Folder 133)
    - Fifteenth Anniversary Show - space proposals and other materials, 1987 (Box 99, Folder 134)
    - Gallery II - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 99, Folder 136)
    - Gallery II - Participant lists, 1990-1995 (Box 99, Folder 137)
    - Gallery II - Resumes, n.d. (Box 99, Folder 138)
    - Gallery II - Resumes, n.d. (Box 99, Folder 139)
    - Lecture series: "A.I.R.: The Early Years", 1996 (Box 99, Folder 140)
    - "One-on-One" - 1987-1988 files (Box 99, Folder 141)
    - "One-on-One" - Correspondence and itineraries, 1987-1990 (Box 99, Folder 142)
    - "One-on-One" - Lottery, 1985-1990 (Box 99, Folder 143)
    - "One-on-One" - Participant evaluation, 1987-1988 (Box 99, Folder 144)
    - "One-on-One" - Participant verification, 1987-1988 (Box 99, Folder 145)
    - Slide series, 1988 (Box 99, Folder 146)
    - Third Thursdays - programming, 1999-2000 (Box 100, Folder 147)
    - Third Thursdays - "Art Songs: Vocal Interpretations in the Visual Arts", 1999 (Box 100, Folder 148)
    - Third Thursdays - Cottingham, Laura: "Not for Sale", 1999 (Box 100, Folder 149)
    - Third Thursdays - "Emergence", 1999 (Box 100, Folder 150)
    - Third Thursdays - Eng, Angie and Debbi Hampton: "Women and Technology", 1999-2000 (Box 100, Folder 151)
    - Third Thursdays - "Leaving the Whitney" panel discussion, 1998-2000 (Box 100, Folder 152)
    - Third Thursdays - McKeown, Erin: "Women on the Verge: Musicians", 1999 (Box 100, Folder 153)
    - Third Thursdays - Millennium Panel, n.d. (Box 100, Folder 154)
    - Third Thursdays - Ringgold, Faith and Nancy Spero, 1999 (Box 100, Folder 155)
    - Third Thursdays - Robbins, Trina: "From Girls to Grrrlz", 1999 (Box 100, Folder 156)
    - Third Thursdays - Senna, Danzy: "Caucasia", 1999 (Box 100, Folder 157)
    - Twenty-fifth Anniversary Show - general files, misc. (Box 100, Folder 158)
    - Twenty-fifth Anniversary Show - Tambrands catalog (Box 100, Folder 159)
    - Workshops, 1982-1987 (Box 4, Folder 160)
    - Misc. - A.I.R. events with unknown dates (Box 4, Folder 161)
    - Misc. - Loan requests made by women to A.I.R., 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 162)
    - Misc. - Proposed exhibitions (not done), 1984-1988 (Box 4, Folder 163)
  - Subseries F: Publications
    - A.I.R. newsletters, Nov. 1974-July 1980 (Box 4, Folder 164)
    - A.I.R. newsletters, Fall 1980-June 1982 (Box 4, Folder 165)
    - A.I.R. newsletters, Oct. 1982-June 1988 (Box 4, Folder 166)
    - A.I.R. newsletters, Oct. 1988-1998 (Box 4, Folder 167)
    - A.I.R. newsletters - used forms, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 168)
    - Catalogs - cassettes, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 169)
    - Catalogs - distribution (Publishing Center), 1981-1984 (Box 4, Folder 170)
    - Catalogs - lists, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 171)
    - Catalogs - orders, 1981-1984 (Box 4, Folder 172)
    - Catalogs - slide sets/skills archive, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 173)
    - Catalogs - video inquiries, 1974-1995 (Box 4, Folder 174)
    - Other publications - Women Artists Newsletter, April 1975-March 1977 (Box 4, Folder 175)
      General note
      contains vol. 1, nos. 1-10; vol. 2, nos. 1-5, 7-9
    - Other publications - Women Artists Newsletter, May 1977-May 1980 (Box 4, Folder 176)
      contains vol. 3, nos. 1-3, 5; vol. 4, nos. 1-3, 6; vol. 5, no. 8; vol. 6, no. 1
    - Other publications - Women in the Arts Foundation newsletters, 1975-1978 (Box 4, Folder 177)
      contains vol. II, no. 7; vol. III, no. 1, 6; vol. IV, no. 1-10; vol. V, no. 1, 3, 5; vol. VII, no. 1
    - Other publications - Women's Caucus for Art newsletters, 1976-1990 (Box 4, Folder 178)
      contains vol. VIII, no. 1; vol. IX, no. 2
    - Other publications - misc. catalogs and brochures (Box 101, Folder 179)
    - Other publications - misc. gallery catalogs (photocopies) (Box 101, Folder 180)
  - Subseries G: Press/Writings (see also Oversize)
    - Press clippings, 1972-1994 (Box 101, Folder 181)
    - Press clippings, 1972-1980 (Box 101, Folder 182)
    - Press clippings, misc. (Box 101, Folder 183)
    - Press clippings, misc. (Box 101, Folder 184)
    - Press clippings, misc. (Box 101, Folder 185)
    - Press clippings, n.d. (Box 101, Folder 186)
    - Press clippings - "Artists as Filmmakers" series, 1975 (Box 101, Folder 187)
    - Press clippings - members at other galleries, 2002-2005 (Box 101, Folder 188)
    - Press clippings - originals, 1972-1975 (Box 101, Folder 189)
    - Press clippings - originals, 1975-1983 (Box 102, Folder 190)
    - Press clippings - panels, 1976-1982 (Box 102, Folder 191)
    - Writings - bibliography, n.d. (Box 102, Folder 192)
    - Writings - pamphlets, 1986(?) (Box 102, Folder 193)
    - Writings - panel transcripts, n.d. (Box 102, Folder 194)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
      [nb: contains diskette]
    - Writings - papers written on A.I.R., n.d. (Box 102, Folder 195)
    - Writings - professional concerns checklist for gallery space, 1993 (Box 102, Folder 196)
    - Writings - slide set essays, n.d. (Box 102, Folder 197)
  - Subseries H: A.I.R. Print Portfolio
    - A.I.R. Print Portfolio, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 198)
    - A.I.R. Print Portfolio, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 199)
    - Portfolio files, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 200)
  - Subseries I: Activism
    - Petitions/protest letters, 1976-1992 (Box 5, Folder 201)
    - Rip-Off File (published by the Ad Hoc Committee of Women Artists), 1972 (Box 5, Folder 202)
    - Rip-Off File - misc. mock-ups, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 203)
  - Subseries J: Notebooks
    - Manual for Biennial Exhibition, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 204)
    - Signature book for exhibitions, 1998-? (Box 5, Folder 205)
  - Subseries K: Misc.
    - Miscellaneous files, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 206)
- Series II: Individual artists (see also Oversize)
  This series contains files pertaining to individual artists who have been represented by the A.I.R. Gallery, such as catalogs, correspondence, and newspaper or magazine articles about the artist. NB: the contents of this series does not comprise a complete list of every artist who has exhibited at A.I.R.. The date that corresponds to each item represents the year the artist joined the gallery, in accordance with the original folder designation. If no such designation existed on the original folder, the date is listed as "n.d." For more information regarding a particular artist not represented here, please contact the A.I.R. Gallery.
  - Achjadi, Diyan, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 207)
  - Archacki, Lorraine, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 208)
  - Attie, Alice, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 209)
  - Attie, Dotty, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 210)
  - Azara, Nancy, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 211)
  - Bachner, Barbara L., n.d. (Box 5, Folder 212)
  - Balmuth, Laurie, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 213)
  - Bas-Cohain, Rachel, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 214)
  - Bas-Cohain, Rachel - artist statements/career summaries, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 214A.)
  - Bas-Cohain, Rachel - correspondence, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 215)
  - Bee, Susan, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 216)
  - Bernardi, Rosemarie, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 217)
  - Bernheim, Stephanie, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 218)
  - Bernier, Isabelle, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 219)
  - Bernstein, Gerda Mayer, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 220)
  - Bernstein, Judith, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 221)
  - Bernstein, Marcy, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 222)
  - Biddle, Liz Surbeck, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 223)
  - Blackwelder, Sarah, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 224)
  - Blum, Sydney, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 225)
  - Bohnen, Blythe, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 226)
  - Boltz, Maude, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 227)
  - Boram-Hays, Carol, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 228)
  - Brant, Sharon, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 229)
  - Byars, Donna, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 230)
  - Carmel, Alexandra, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 231)
  - Chao, Hui-Lin, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 232)
  - Craven, Leigh, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 233)
  - Dachman, Ivy, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 234, Box Shared Fales 115, Folder 1)
  - d'Arrigo, Ellen, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 235)
  - Daw, Leila, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 236)
  - Denes, Agnes, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 237)
  - Dienes, Sari, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 238)
  - Dorosh, Daria, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 239)
  - Dorosh, Daria, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 240)
    [contains CD-ROM: Delaware Valley Arts Alliance, The Gallery Program: "SHIFT: The Work of Daria Dorosh"]
  - Draney, Sarah, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 241)
  - Dunkelman, Loretta, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 242)
  - Edelson, Mary Beth, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 243)
  - Edelson, Mary Beth, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 244)
  - Eisenstein, Sandra (Box 7, Folder 245)
  - Eng, Angie, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 246)
    Fuji T-10 VHS videorecording with annotations: "Angie Eng Demo"; "Image Bank" removed from folder. Please see Series VI: Videorecordings.
  - Eng, Angie, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 247)
  - Gifford, Jessie Nebraska, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 248)
  - Gifford, Jessie Nebraska, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 249)
  - Gilmor, Jane, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 250)
  - Gilmor, Jane, n.d. (Box 103, Folder 251)
    3M T-60 VHS videorecording with annotations: "1996/97 McKnight Fellowship Artists 32 minutes"; "(Gilmor 1st 6 min.)" removed from folder. Please see Series VI: Videorecordings.
  - Goldberg, Lenore, 1980 (Box 103, Folder 252)
  - Goodwin, Erin, n.d. (Box 103, Folder 253)
  - Granne, Regina, n.d. (Box 103, Folder 254)
  - Grigoriadis, Mary, 1972 (Box 103, Folder 255)
  - Grigoriadis, Mary, 1972 (Box 103, Folder 256)
  - Grinell, Barbara, n.d. (Box 103, Folder 257)
  - Haberl, Judy, n.d. (Box 103, Folder 258)
  - Hambleton, Susan, 1986 (Box 103, Folder 259)
  - Hammond, Harmony, 1976 (Box 103, Folder 260)
  - Hampton, Debra (Box 103, Folder 261)
  - Hartman, Tanya, n.d. (Box 103, Folder 262)
  - Haskell, Jane, 1988 (Box 103, Folder 263)
  - Healy, Anne, 1972 (Box 103, Folder 264)
  - Heinrich, Adrienne, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 265)
  - Hettmansperger, Sue, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 266)
  - Hofkin, Ann Ginsburgh, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 267)
  - Horvay, Martha, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 268)
  - Itami, Michi, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 269)
  - James, Laurace, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 270)
  - Jolicoeur, Nicole, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 271)
  - Kavanagh, Ursula, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 272)
  - Kazuko, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 273)
  - Kim, Juri, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 274)
  - Kniesel, Leslie, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 275)
  - Korf, Kumi, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 276)
  - Kramer, Louise, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 277)
  - Krantz, Claire Wolf, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 278)
  - Kumata, Carol, n.d. (Box 97, Folder 279)
  - Lasch, Pat, 1974 (Box 97, Folder 280)
  - Lovelarkin, Salli, n.d. (Box 97, Folder 281)
  - Manion-Artz, Sheila, n.d. (Box 97, Folder 282)
  - Martin, Carolyn, 1988 (Box 97, Folder 283)
  - Martin, Carolyn, 1988 (Box 97, Folder 284)
    VHS videorecording separated out from Series II, Box 8, Folder 283
    T-15 VHS videorecording: "Lineage: Carolyn Martin 1995" removed from folder. Please see Series VI: Videorecordings.
  - Maughelli, Mary, n.d. (Box 97, Folder 285)
  - Mayer, Rosemary, 1972 (Box 97, Folder 286)
  - McCagg, Louise, 1993 (Box 97, Folder 287)
  - Mendieta, Ana, 1978 (Box 97, Folder 288)
  - Merriman, Constance, n.d. (Box 97, Folder 289)
  - Morrow, Nancy, n.d. (Box 97, Folder 290)
  - Neal, Mo, n.d. (Box 97, Folder 291)
  - Netzer, Sylvia, 1994 (Box 97, Folder 292)
  - Norvell, Patsy, 1972 (Box 97, Folder 293)
  - Oritsky, Mimi, n.d. (Box 98, Folder 294)
  - Pachner, Ann, n.d. (Box 98, Folder 295)
  - Pindell, Howardena, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 296)
  - Racette, Elizabeth, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 297)
  - Reichek, Elaine, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 298)
  - Riese, Beatrice, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 299)
  - Ross, Carol, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 300)
  - Ross, Sheila, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 301)
  - Ross, Sheila, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 302)
    contents of this folder separated out from Series II, Box 9, Folder 301
    General
    1 Fuji HQ T-120 VHS videorecording, annotated: "Sheila Ross Environmental Installations Environment, Photography and Spoken Text by Sheila Ross Music by Mary Jane Leach (14 min. 20 sec.) (c) Sheila Ross 2006"; removed from folder. Please see Series VI: Videorecordings.
    [contents: 2x700MB CompUSA CD-Rs, annotated: "A.I.R. Gallery Archive (c) Sheila Ross 2006 Sheila Ross _ Archive 7.23.06" (disc 1 further annotated: "2006.1"; disc 2 further annotated "2006.2"); 1 CompUSA 4.7GB/120 min DVD-R, annotated: "Life on Earth is brief II (c) Sheila Ross 2006"]
  - Roux, Barbara, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 303)
  - Samuels, Diane, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 304)
  - Schaumburger, Ann, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 305)
  - Schneider, Kathleen, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 306)
  - Seeman, Rebecca, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 307)
  - Shaw, Francie, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 308)
  - Shepley, Julia, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 309)
  - Shicoff, Rochelle, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 310)
  - Sivak, Marie, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 311)
  - Sleigh, Sylvia, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 312)
  - Smith, Elizabeth Munro, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 313)
  - Solomon, Elke, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 314)
  - Sosin, Georgette, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 315)
  - Spero, Nancy, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 316)
  - Steinhardt, Alice, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 318)
  - Stevens, Jane, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 319)
  - Storrow, Nancy, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 320)
  - Strasen, Barbara, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 321)
  - Streed, Crit, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 322)
  - Takenaga, Barbara, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 323)
  - Tharp, Linda (Box 10, Folder 324)
  - Torres-Yap, Fay, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 325)
  - Vail, Clover, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 326)
  - Visscher, Jantje, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 327)
  - Walker, Meg, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 328)
  - Wasserman, Deborah (Box 10, Folder 329)
  - Webber, Tenesh, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 330)
  - Weidner, Mary, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 331)
  - Weigl, Jean Kondo (Box 10, Folder 332)
  - Weinrib, Madeline, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 333)
  - Wells, Taryn, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 334)
  - White, Nancy Lockwood, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 335)
  - Wilding, Faith, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 336)
  - Williams, Susan, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 337)
  - Wilson, Ann, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 338)
  - Yntema, Janise, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 339)
  - Zechel, Elizabeth, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 340)
  - Zucker, Barbara, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 341)
- Series III: Exhibition files
  This series contains postcards, flyers, catalogs, correspondence and other information relating to specific exhibitions at A.I.R. or hosted by A.I.R. at other venues. The date that corresponds to each item in this series represents the duration of the exhibition, in accordance with the original folder designation. Not every exhibition in A.I.R.'s history is represented; for more details, please consult the exhibition schedules contained within this series.
  - Subseries A: Exhibitions held at A.I.R. (see also Oversize)
    - Exhibition schedules, 1972-1994 (Box 10, Folder 342)
    - Exhibition schedules, 1972-1998 (Box 10, Folder 343)
    - "Ten Gallery Artists", Sept. 16-Oct. 4, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 344)
    - "Ten Gallery Artists", Sept. 16, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 345)
      1 Maxell P/I Plus T-30 VHS videorecording: "1972 Opening and Discussion" removed from folder. Please see Series VI: Videorecordings.
    - Anne Healy/Louise Kramer, Oct. 7-25, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 346)
    - Susan Williams/Agnes Denes, Oct. 28-Nov. 15, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 347)
    - Barbara Zucker/Blythe Bohnen, Nov. 18-Dec. 6, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 348)
    - Dotty Attie/Mary Grigoriadis, Dec. 9-27, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 349)
    - "Open A.I.R.: A.I.R. Members Invite 20 Women Artists", Dec. 30, 1972-Jan. 10, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 350)
    - Harmony Hammond, Jan. 13-31, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 351)
    - Patsy Norvell/Laurace James, Feb. 3-21, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 352)
    - Rachel bas-Cohain/Loretta Dunkelman, Feb. 24-Mar. 14, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 353)
    - Nancy Spero/Maude Boltz, Mar. 17-Apr. 4, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 354)
    - Daria Dorosh/Nancy Kitchel, Apr. 7-25, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 355)
    - Judith Bernstein/Rosemary Mayer, Apr. 28-May 16, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 356)
    - "Ten Gallery Artists", May 19-June 6, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 357)
    - "Invitational", June 9-27, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 358)
    - "Invitational: Women Artists from Washington, D.C.", Sep. 8-26, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 359)
    - "Ten Gallery Artists", Sep. 29-Oct.17, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 360)
    - Judith Bernstein, Oct. 20-Nov. 7, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 361)
    - Sari Dienes, Nov. 10-28, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 362)
    - Pat Lasch, Dec. 1-19, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 363)
    - "A.I.R. Group Show", Dec. 22, 1973-Jan. 2, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 364)
    - Anne Healy, Jan. 5-23, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 365)
    - Howardena Pindell, Jan. 26-Feb. 13, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 366)
    - Loretta Dunkelman, Feb. 16-Mar. 6, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 367)
    - Maude Boltz/Daria Dorosh, Mar. 9-27, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 368)
    - "Invitational: Four Artists - Cynthia Carlson, Joyce Kozloff, Athena Tacha, Ann Wilson", Mar. 30-Apr. 17, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 369)
    - Blythe Bohnen, Apr. 20-May 8, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 370)
    - Barbara Zucker, May 11-29, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 371)
    - "A.I.R. Invitational", June 18-July 2, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 372)
    - Sylvia Sleigh, Sep. 14-Oct. 2, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 373)
    - "10-10-10-10-10-10", Oct. 5-23, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 374)
    - Rachel bas-Cohain, Oct. 26-Nov. 13, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 375)
    - Dotty Attie, Nov. 16-Dec. 4, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 376)
    - Nancy Spero, Dec. 7-25, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 377)
    - "Invitational: A.I.R. Apprentices", Dec. 27, 1974-Jan. 1, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 378)
    - Mary Grigoriadis, Jan. 4-22, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 379)
    - Louise Kramer, Jan. 25-Feb. 12, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 380)
    - Laurace James, Feb. 15-Mar. 15, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 381)
    - "Invitational", Mar. 8-26, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 382)
    - "Invitational" Selection by Susan Williams, Mar. 29-Apr. 16, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 383)
    - Kazuko, Apr. 19-May 7, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 384)
    - "A.I.R. Invitational Show", May 10-28, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 385)
    - "A.I.R. Gallery Group Show", May 31-June 18, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 386)
    - Mary Beth Edelson, Sep. 13-Oct. 8, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 387)
    - Clover Vail, Oct. 11-Nov. 5, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 388)
    - Sari Dienes, Nov. 8-Dec. 3, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 389)
    - Patsy Norvell, Dec. 6-31, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 390)
    - "Invitational", Jan. 3-28, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 391)
    - Sylvia Sleigh, Jan. 31-Feb. 25, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 392)
    - Daria Dorosh, Feb. 28-Mar. 24, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 393)
    - Blythe Bohnen, Mar. 27-Apr. 21, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 394)
    - Maude Boltz, Apr. 24-May 19, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 395)
    - "Combative Acts, Profiles and Voices: An Exhibition of Women Artists from Paris", May 22 - June 16, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 396)
    - Nancy Spero, Sep. 11-Oct. 6, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 397)
    - Rachel bas-Cohain, Oct. 3-Nov. 3, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 398)